<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Daily News</string>
    <string name="sample_post_excerpt">In the two decades since 9/11, governments and media organizations hostile to Islam have produced non-stop anti-Muslim propaganda. This propaganda has been used to justify US wars in places like Iraq and Afghanistan. It has been used justify repressive legislation...
</string>
    <string name="sample_article">In the two decades since 9/11, governments and media organizations hostile to Islam have produced non-stop anti-Muslim propaganda.\n\nThis propaganda has been used to justify US wars in places like Iraq and Afghanistan. It has been used justify repressive legislation against Muslim minorities in non-Muslims countries like France, India, and Israel. Such propaganda has likewise been used to justify repressive legislation against the general population in Muslim countries governed by secular authoritarian regimes.\n\nMuch anti-Muslim propaganda centers on the claim that the traditional Quranic doctrine on jihad legitimates terrorism. It legitimates the 9/11 attacks, as well as subsequent terrorist attacks carried out by groups like al-Qaeda and Daesh (ISIS).\n\nIt is false that jihad doctrine legitimates such terrorism. However, to this day, this point has been not explained with sufficient clarity. Consequently, there is significant confusion on the matter.\n\nIslam and Violence\nThe first step is to clarify Islam’s stance on violence.\n\nIslam is concerned with politics and government. Every government endorses violence in the form of law and warfare. Governments must utilize violence to enforce laws and punish criminals. Warfare utilizes violence to defend a people and its way of life. Warfare is also used to advance the interests of that people in its struggle with rival peoples for power and resources.\n\nIslam endorses a specific form of government (khilafa) which imposes Sharia. The government defends the Muslim people (Umma) and its way of life (Islam). Warfare (jihad) is also used to advance the interests of the Muslims in their struggle with rival peoples for power and resources. These other peoples use war to establish power over Muslims, and Muslims use war to establish power over them. This is the nature of politics – a view usually referred to as “political realism” or “Realpolitik.” All governments, not just Islamic governments, operate in similar fashion.\n\nFurthermore, all governments, not just Islamic governments, are based on hierarchical authority. The ruler (imam) and other high ranking political authorities are given responsibility for applying the law and waging war. To successfully apply laws or wage wars, careful planning and cooperation are necessary. Political authorities ensure the necessary planning and cooperation.</string>
</resources>